Hello, definitely learn in Hindi,
welcome to the next episode. In this, in a
few episodes, we are
learning to make complex structure complex sentences in German.
First of all, we learned 10 years, problem,
okay, after that we learned plus infinitive,
and this Sunday is a very important episode, in
that point, this point is there and
what is the meaning of I dar and not only but also what is called dar, the
conjugation turnover of dar, we will learn on Sunday, okay,
in the same channel, today we are going to learn those which are not used more than small kal, the same
relatives, which you will learn,
what are relatives, so if you say that you Kedar is the
boy who plays cricket, then now we do
not say it like this, Elaichi, he
plays cricket in Rangrezz serial,
what will happen to him in English, the character is the man who
plays cricket,
Sanjay Tiwari, the man who plays cricket,
who speaks like this or who will say the
character is the man, I will rotate it for a minute
because on
one side, the character of the subject is
developed at this time, why did my play with home IPL
wheat happen because after a minute, so
if you see in this, what did you do  I am etc.,
we did it, similarly
in German this concept is called relatives and for that we
use relative problem, there is problem
in relative pronouns,
so what is good for us is that the
problem is the same as the one we used in Southern,
if you are seeing it in the table, then the
best thing about this session is
that if your case is clear then
you are not going to learn anything new today, you are
not going to learn anything new in this pimple, so if you look
at the stable, then this relative appointment table is almost exactly
like a tumor for you, the party alliance, if you
see the pain, Hindi Rashi, dam dam, it was just one
day and when I give pain,
leave the tension of logging in, no one talks about
that character, I am the man, let's talk,
sentence just completed but first year
important and get it ready, I am
fine, you do each step by step, so first of all,
in the nominative, see that at this time the nail plate, here at
this time the playlist, so keep one thing simple and small  It is
like wife shadow sunshine
is lage it happens instantly and essay
meaning what is in sentence then what is it or
normal subscribe
first is simple the character is da handkerchief
character will come mostly in this period same
here by going to my details I have nominated male and
nominal male that is why the
character is Dharmanand subscribe what will happen
subscribe this is the same way subscribe subscribe
and subscribe the let's see the
character is the man who
turned my tweet minute so in that what is the character in the hour what will happen to
you in the definition so what will happen to
Kedar this Armaan collector will come to you
tubewell den this track
I will give you in detail what will happen to the
poem this intense shool isht
because it is a positive female lead to
meet 2010 cant dance track again
keeps you steady off the tube light
because let's do Kedar this Mahal Vidhu
my play again with German what is
mit-mit what happens don't you that is why
this Dhar this Dar Mount Abu me Dekho dam this
appeal similarly to Vikas poem this Deep
from meet there  If you have typing skills then
similarly to boost 10 to 20 minutes
dam ishq pillar rate right now just to
clear the concept and complete the artist
I
was giving you this step of genitive but to
say this also the character is the match award is
red so what will happen the character usage is the same I just
called from that
in English also if it does not tick for a while then
go and see what is on 10 it is
difficult how to rotate according to this day the
system to rotate the simplest but in this
person you are ever going to do Bigg Boss
that the center is the man whose car is red
whose watch is red subscribe if you
think that you do not need to remember this also then you have to
change the subscription
because if you like this sexual
quit skilled this horse now there is one more small
concept Ankush and relative I will quickly
cover that meaning but you should see this
because you feel a little in one and a half light that the
boy who plays cricket
Kedar set if you talk to him right now then what will the other person
understand about what he is talking  There is
also in English, The Man Who Plays Cricket, in this
you do not talk like this, right,
in German you will not talk like normal,
but on the contrary, just players, Ratan set,
how will this Darman be, then I will give two
substances in this middle,
New Delhi cricket split, Ist character
creation, daily printed salwar, in a short time,
you will never use this yourself, but just
suppose you have ever
seen something of this deleted in the exam, then you
should know why it is late twice, so
basically I have put it in the middle, but as this
contest in general is not much used
100, but it is good to know why, you all must have
understood this connection, this Sunday we are going to
learn a very important concept, as I said, Swan Telecom Sector, hand,
we meet in that condition, thank you